CHRISTIAN CORONA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Buenos Aires, Argentina · +54 9 1132006857 · <u>chriscoronab@gmail.com</u> LinkedIn: <u>chriscoronab</u> · GitHub: <u>chriscoronab</u> · Portfolio: <u>christiancorona.vercel.app</u>

Full Stack Developer with over 1 year of experience in developing intuitive and efficient web applications, using technologies such as **JavaScript**, **TypeScript**, **React**, **Next.js**, **Node.js** and **Express**. Specialized in creating high-performance solutions, ensuring code quality through best practices and attention to detail. Committed to continuous learning to expand my technical skills and collaborate on challenging projects.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

No Country Remote

Full Stack Developer

September 2024 – Present

- Participated in the development of two web apps, Best Friend and Soundbit, collaborating with a multidisciplinary team to create functional and innovative solutions.
- Contributed to the implementation of key features and code optimization, applying modern technologies and best development practices.
- Focused primarily on frontend development, using technologies such as **JavaScript**, **React**, **Next.js**, **Tailwind** and **Bootstrap** to create dynamic, intuitive and responsive interfaces.
- Implemented Agile methodologies (Scrum) in project management, ensuring timely deliveries.

Best Friend's link: <u>findyourbestfriend.vercel.app</u> – Repository: <u>Best Friend</u> Soundbit's link: <u>soundbitmusic.vercel.app</u> – Repository: <u>Soundbit</u>

Bodega Limbo Remote

Frontend Developer

June 2023 – December 2023

- Developed Bodega Limbo's website with an e-commerce platform, significantly increasing the sales of its products.
- Consolidated the brand and improved business visibility by implementing an attractive and functional website, achieving greater digital presence and facilitating interaction with customers.
- Implemented a responsive interface adapted to multiple devices using **JavaScript** and **React**.
- Facilitated communication between customers and the company by developing a contact form that sends inquiries directly to their inbox, optimizing customer service.
- Resolved functional issues, contributing to the success of the company and user satisfaction. Link: bodegalimbo.com.ar Repository: Bodega Limbo

EDUCATION

CODERHOUSE August 2022 – March 2024

Full Stack Development Career (Certificate)

Web Development – JavaScript – React Js –Backend Programming

• Ranked in the **Top 10** in the 4 courses of the Full Stack Development Career.

SKILLS

- Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Next.js, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material UI, shadon.
- Backend: Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Firebase, Passport.js, JWT, OAuth.
- **DevOps:** Docker, Kubernetes.
- Version Control: Git, GitHub.
- Collaboration Tools: Slack, Discord, Trello, GitHub Projects, GitHub Issues.
- Methodologies: Scrum, Agile, Kanban.
- **Soft Skills:** Teamwork, leadership, effective communication, proactivity, determination.

LANGUAGES

- **Spanish:** Native.
- English: Advanced C1 (EF Certificate).